Thank you.
Bye.
right
Thank you.
Amen.
I'm going to make it easy for me to cut.
I'm going to get my hair off the top.
This is for me.
I started to cut my hair off the top.
Thank you.
.
so
So, remember, you just said I'd be able to have the same word.
Thank you.
All right.
Alright.
Thank you.
and
This is going to get us into a video.
.
Thank you.
Is that right?
right
is
Thank you.
What about this one?
and
We need to follow those things.
You can take this question.
You can take the first question.
Please come back with me.
That's fine.
Thank you.
So, this is a special version.
Well, I'm gonna ask you to do this one.
And I'm just gonna ask you to do that.
So, what do you think is that?
Actually, that's what you're gonna do.
I'm gonna ask you to do this one.
so
It is important.
is there a lot of time
really
is
Thank you.
and
so that
Thank you.
is
I'm going to go ahead and do that.
that i need you to do with any more work
...
what
Thank you.
.
Let's go.
Thank you.
Good night.
as we see this whole match.
All right.
Thank you.
So that's the person who's not in place.
All right?
Thank you so much.
Thank you.
And you're hearing more.
I will also press the button to press the button to press the button to press the button,
then press the button to press the button.
It will press the button to press the button to press the button.
I will press the button to press the button to press the button.
I see this.
Thank you.
So that's that's okay.
That's that's in the ground.
So what's your take?
I will take you.
And I will take you.
So why?
I will take you.
and
Thank you.
Everything is done.
but
And let's see.
Thank you.
.
Okay, we have a couple questions.
Thank you.
Puck up!
so
I think now the start of the presentation is going to be quite important.
I think the first time I see my first time I see my first time next time.
I am going to go through the process.
Thank you.
I'm going to ask you a question.
...
4, 5, 6, 7, 7, 8, 8, 8, 9, 10, 12, 13, 14, 14, 15, 16, 17, 18, 19, 20, 21, 21, 22, 22, 23, 24, 25, 26, 27, 29, 27, 29, 28, 29, 29, 30, 30, 31, 32, 32, 32, 33, 32, 33, 34, 34, 35, 35, 35, 36, 37, 37, 39, 40, 32, 34, 35, 36, 35, 37, 38, 39, 40, 35, 39, 40, 40, 40, 41, 51, 32, 34, 45, 36, 38, 39, 39, 40, 42, 45, 41, 41, 42, 41, 41, 42, 41, 42, 42, 42, 43, 41, 42, 43, 42, 42, 42, 42, 42, 42, 43, 43, 44, 41, 42, 43, 42, 45, 42, 42, 41, 42
I am the first person.
This is a place where I can live in my home,
but this is a place where I can live in my home.
Thank you.
So, I'm going to get a little bit of a of the
So that's the impression you want to be able to use the
Let's pray.
Thank you.
.
And we're going to need to find it.
And then ready.
.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
And in the arms of the body, I'm sorry.
The other is the third one.
Thank you, everyone.
Thank you.
so
that
the
your
Thank you.
so
All right.
Thank you.
You are welcome.
.
Thank you.
OK, thank you, thank you.
.
Thank you.
Now.
Amen.
This is a great and special program.
Okay.
So that's it.
Sorry.
Hello.
Thank you.
I'm just going to show you.
I'm just going to show you guys, and we're going to show you guys that I'm going to show
you guys a little bit later.
I'm just going to show you guys like this.
I'm just going to show you guys.
Yeah, I'm going to show you guys a little bit more.
I'm just going to show you guys a little bit more.
Oh yeah.
That one.
Yeah, I just like my own.
I just like that.
Yeah.
That's great.
I know.
I emailed text.
I'm sure you're right.
Yeah.
Yes.
Hi.
I don't know who wants guys, the other ones.
I know one of them was like, oh, but.
For now, I'd just say in the final project,
In the final project, she has slides, and also a doc describing how she wants the format
for everything and what she expects from it.
3 to 5 pages, fonts that's set, space, including everything.
I'm going to try and pick out a couple of things.
sections of that before this weekend.
How's it work? Because by next time
we have the
end of the park that's going to take the most time.
Once we get the dock fully done, I can probably get the slideshow done.
With decent pictures,
more editing and things. When we do that, I just figured
I'll let you know what my game plan is.
I'm going to try to get ahead of a bunch of other projects
so that I can just take time for this.
I'll be quite smart on that.
I'm not going to do that right now.
So I'll check it out.
I'll get an overview of how we should format it.
And then we'll go over here, too.
Yeah.
We'll see what we can do.
I'm not too concerned by like how much or like how little work I do.
Yeah.
At the end of the day, it doesn't seem like too much for the group.
Like, even when you look at it as like a research project, it's still not that much.
But the fact that we get up to four people per group is almost like to make chefs for
Like we can't have all four people working on the dog and all four people working on the
sign thing or have to commit something but just a scientist or just a guy.
Or like relegated people.
Yeah.
Well, all four of us are being presenting so we need to kind of figure out how we're going
to present.
I don't care about the whole student self evaluation evaluation.
I just wanted to talk to you about that.
I've eyes, I can't do it.
I can't do it.
I'm saying
what would I be talking about?
Yeah, let's go.
And
No
um
i mean oh
yeah
all of them are very excited.
You see what it is?
I'm going to stay here.
Oh, yeah.
Okay.
I think it's easier.
I'm not allowed to work with, and I don't mean.
You probably have a few minutes here.
Same time.
I don't need to wear to wear to wear my mask.
I don't need to wear my mask.
Thank you.
It's a final one.
I don't want to wear my mask.
Phone rings.
Why not?
Yeah
Just let me set this up
I should like
What?
Okay, so I'm sitting like a
I have to say one thing
I will keep a little
I am
I will say you
You know I want you to.
I want you to.
You know.
I'm sorry.
I'm not.
Be careful.
Try it.
Thank you.
you
It's so cute.
I'm just cute.
Thank you.
Do I need to get a bit?
That's good.
it's different
Okay.
All right.
you know I'm like you know I'll create your work my Instagram is just a guy I
They go for effect, I see what they say.
I'm going to be so serious.
Can guys speak before you listen?
You did?
So that'd be so good.
And that meant you listen.
Okay.
Thank you so much.
I'll just be right back.
Yes, I'll get into it.
I think I'm going to be at this point.
It's going to be a little better.
I think it's going to be a little better.
I'm going to be a little better.
I don't think I'm going to be a little better.
Thank you.
It is a very difficult time.
so
The next one is the left.
and
Okay.
.
Thank you.
and
please
Okay.
Thank you.
This is a work that's important to be involved in the way the body is very clear to the body.
So, there's two points here, and then, one step,
one step, one step, one step,
one step, right there, right there,
one step.
One step, one step, one step,
one step, one step, one step,
I'm not going to be able to do this.
I'm going to be able to do this.
I'm going to be able to do this because I'm not going to be able to do this.
I'm not going to be able to do this.
I'm going to be able to do this.
you
Thank you.
Okay.
There it is.
Thank you.
See, I'm going to talk to you about your own personal life.
I'm going to talk to you about your own personal life.
This is one of the most common things that you're not always
talking about your own personal life.
We're going to talk to you about your own personal life,
and we're going to talk to you about your own personal life.
We're going to talk to you about your own personal life.
Thank you.
Okay.
I'm going to get it.
Thank you.
Yeah.
And so, for you to see,
for you to see,
Okay, okay.
Thank you.
And that's.
so
Okay.
Is that ok?
Thank you.
Keep it.
to take it.
He is really dependent on the human being.
He is a human being.
so
Thank you.
See you again.
okay
here
All right.
Thank you.
You can't.
All right, I'm going to go to the next section.
Thank you.
All right.
Okay.
Thank you.
All right.
I just need to be able to put it back in.
And they're just working on the left.
Left.
Okay.
All right.
Let's go.
Thank you.
And, and and and yeah, yeah.
Yeah.
you
and the other way we are just going to be going to be transparent.
I am going to try and use the same thing here.
It's easy to do.
Yeah.
so
Thank you.
It's like a bridge.
It is like a bridge.
Right?
Thank you.
Okay.
I think it was very important.
So now we're going to look at the hinterland.
Thank you.
.
it
I'm going to take you to the next hour.
Thank you.
I don't know.
.
Okay.
All right.
I am going to be right.
you
Thank you.
...
Good night.
So, I'm going to get my hands up and get them done.
I'm going to get my hands up and I'm going to get them done.
Thank you.
...
.
Thank you.
So, let's just start a little bit earlier.
Now I'm going to go ahead and see how to change this part.
I can see how to change the mind and the movement.
I'm going to get into it and see how to change the mind.
I can see how to change it.
I'm going to move on to the right of the movement.
Okay.
Thank you.
I'm sorry.
so
Thank you.
.
...
Thank you.
So, since I'm going to do this , I will start this with a little bit of a motion.
I will say the motion is fine, I will start this with a little bit of a motion.
So, it is I will start with a motion.
So, this will be the motion.
Your body is only based on your body and body.
Your body is also based on the body.
Your body is not based on your body.
Your body is based on your body.
So, you can see it here.
Thank you.
.
I am going to make a little bit of a small piece.
I am going to add a little bit of a small piece of paper.
I am going to add one piece of paper.
Thank you.
I am going to stick with the hand.
...
Please follow me on the follow-up.
Thank you.
okay
I'm going to go back to the next day, that's the Q&A, the latest Thursday.
Thank you.
This is my friend.
okay
Thank you.
I agree with that.
So, let's try to make the final cut.
It's a little tricky.
I'm gonna start a little tricky.
All right.
If you want to make sure you're going to get a little bit stuck, you're going to get
this little thing and the other thing that you're going to need to do is try to get
this little thing out of the way you can go to the side.
I'm going to go to the side of the side, but I'm going to go take this little bit of
the side.
There you go.
Oh.
But it wasn't.
It was good.
Oh, wait, did you say .
I'm looking at .
Oh, and .
Oh, .
I don't think .
Okay.
Just have to be good at this little talk.
to the end.
Next,
And so we're going to start with the whole panel.
Thank you.
So I'm going to ask you a question, where are we actually looking at?
It's great.
Thank you.
You said, I'll be playing.
He has art.
He looks like a flyer.
Solid, solid, solid.
Solid.
i want you to focus
she needs to burn
for that
i do
for three
hey
sit down
you can do
for it
for you
i do
But what do I need to read this from?
.
Read your head.
Yeah.
Okay.
That's fun.
okay
yeah
oh
.
I'm a hazard .
I'm a hazard my tooth.
You're a hazard to everybody around you.
.
Thank you.
Oh, okay.
Am I human or not?
I don't think so.
That is a fat ass.
I wasn't calling you a fat ass.
Yeah I'm trying to say something right now.
Thank you.
Amen.
Let's go.
I'll see you next time.
All right.
I could not cut the tape, but I would not have to do this.
And then we will cut the tape.
I used the tape to make a tape on the tape.
The tape is the tape.
I do not have to cut the tape.
Thank you.
...
So...
What is your name?
Thank you.
I'm going to take a few minutes.
Let's go.
Thank you.
so
I'm going to take care.
I'm going to ask you to see a couple of questions.
Thank you.
So, let's go ahead and cut it back.
the back side is here.
do
Thank you.
All right.
Let's go.
Thank you.
to the right.
so
I will get one of those things, one of them is what's happening?
Just one of the other things.
Just one of them.
I think it was just one of them.
It was about a year until the first year of the year.
Really?
Yeah.
Well, I don't know about that.
Thank you.
so
Let's go.
Thank you.
The flow of the flow of the flow of the flow of the flow, the flow of the flow.